Shubhendu, I
understand what I have in mind, we
need some more clarity in this, so for that I will
install it, for that generation you have
run that short covering, I think this can
come to our house somewhere on Defence Road to see that
yours, now let's move ahead and talk about our son
Vikram, Rajesh Thakur,
Deshraj ji, your top in this couple will
work, I will
go to the village soon, the stoploss is around 11447, Rafi lakh
is around 12345, 1515 I
should go here, so it is here,
yes then remember this topic, there is pressure on one side, let me
show you your skin,
tractor here, there is a statement of Iraq's present,
that very close to the removal
of few sentences in this flower country, come,
travel typing's comment is very
important, he has said that we are very
optimistic about this, the
reception from us is that of removing cricket in the time period,
which will be
very important on the recovery of the character's own fatwa, a
statement very important and agencies
see the results, state  I have said, and
remember that the most important aspect of what we export to Iran is
rise to connect with anger, valid
inference, and care. Khushi Ram Bihari Lal will
ask for this, and this will
open Dawat once in life with friends.
What is the benefit doing? And entered a setting.
After all,
using 727 quantities. Yes, its
price vacation is quite strong. Price will be
part of the mission. 1738. Quickly,
this hobby of theirs is difficult to do. Back
possible. If you are finding it absolutely possible,
Dawat looks quite good. And
from 14 students, Company Law and
Information Minister, on the chart, so I have
seen, then definitely a buying
advice here. 1714 will support 846. And
in Position Hunter Cricket, this possible is a
very good stock. You have caught the
biggest position in Dawat and Indian exports that you will see to Iran.
In the week, Basmati
rice is written, which you will see Hunter exporting Dawat and many others.
Afternoon there you are already
seeing a great moment on the screen
of the block in front of me which is 83
lakh and currently explained seven lakh
and the bell is coming in front of you, here in
front of you
see the price of additive foods has now reached the all time high that
you will see it coming in May 2018 and the all time
is
170 so you see the price of May 2018
that cream is seen groaning and
you are seeing the highest level of January 12,
good, very great moment and the price is
sitting in front of you the volume has reached
61 lakh six language areas often the record is
seen going to 108
absolutely and exploited a very tremendous breakup is
happening volume see Chiffon has returned
Masti Chappell Bigg Boss has written
that melt kabbas start, there is a fast of 173 in
front of Shyam, when will the internal sugar
start, watch it because
in June 2017 America was in the top 10 and till then
they will lose weight like a fall because
friends recruitment is on level  If you are seen emphasizing on it
then keep it at 7120 and
here also good growth candidate Mukesh Kumar
Mishra
Shukra Hello channels, do you see
similar question in the stock market, after that
once you get clear protein
that your net has spread, this is yesterday morning city in
which many Air High Court has sentenced, I do
not believe this news that this
bail to wife 91 lakhs, it seems that there will be no
big deal in Delhi regarding gold,
100, no one is saying that this thyroid will become a
million pimples because you see, you who are
from the city who are positive and they
come in multi-mantra form, they were top recover, and
if till the price for germination vkontakte and
many people will try to participate in it,
cut the first injection,
how did it happen, then according to me friends,
you will see the trajectory of Bhagwat-224
in the clear latest, there will be a problem here, so
if they
establish this and 221 then it will be 300
and 225 towards 274  There can be a
very-very chance that hectare land can be acquired. For a long time, you are
seeing news about rice toss.
In the morning session, you saw Sumit Kumar doing the
encounter and the
news that was in front of France was that the purchase price of the Government of Africa's capital, the
Food Corporation of India, was
₹2000 per quintal and here
you can see it coming, production of
account holder, so that morning news is being seen running for
you positively and rice thoughts.